<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<preface xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
    xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" version="5.0"
    xml:id="ch_image-service-dev-overview.html">
    <title>Preface</title>
<?dbhtml stop-chunking?>
    <para>OpenStack Image Service offers retrieval, storage, and
        metadata assignment for your images that you want to run in
        your OpenStack cloud. The project is code-named Glance. </para>
    <para>OpenStack Image service enables users to store and retrieve
        images through a simple Web Service (ReST: Representational
        State Transfer) interface. </para>
    <para>For more details on the OpenStack Image service,
        please refer to <link xlink:href="http://docs.openstack.org/developer/glance/"
            >docs.openstack.org/developer/glance/</link>
    </para>
    <para>We welcome feedback, comments, and bug reports at <link
            xlink:href="http://bugs.launchpad.net/glance"
            >bugs.launchpad.net/glance</link>. </para>
    <section xml:id="glance-api-intended-audience">
        <title>Intended Audience</title>
        <para>This guide is intended to assist software developers who
            want to develop applications using the OpenStack Image
            Service API. It fully documents the ReST application
            programming interface (API) that allows developers to
            interact with the storage components of the OpenStack
            Image system. To use the information provided
            here, you should first have a general understanding of the
            OpenStack Image Service and have access to an installation
            of OpenStack Image Service. You should also be familiar
            with: </para>
        <itemizedlist spacing="compact">
            <listitem>
                <para>ReSTful web services</para>
            </listitem>
            <listitem>
                <para>HTTP/1.1</para>
            </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
    </section>
    <section xml:id="doc-change-history">
        <title>Document Change History</title>
        <para>This version of the reference replaces and
            obsoletes all previous versions. The most recent
            changes are described in the table below:</para>
        <?rax revhistory?>
        <!-- Table generated in output from revision element in the book element -->
    </section>
</preface>
